{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "61 + 54",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 55",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 79",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 26",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 47",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 40",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 56",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 82",
      "answer": 164
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 40",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 77",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 32",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 85",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 89",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 3",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 14",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 7",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 35",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 22",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 1",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 27",
      "answer": 33
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 1",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 83",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 58",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 55",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 46",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 63",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 68",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 35",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 96",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 71",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 73",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 9",
      "answer": 66
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 91",
      "answer": 185
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 74",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 94",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 22",
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 69",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 23",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 45",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 32",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 94",
      "answer": 184
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 97",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 82",
      "answer": 153
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 81",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 47",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 22",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 90",
      "answer": 177
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 5",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 85",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 92",
      "answer": 146
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 13",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 34",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 38",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 94",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 2",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 26",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 22",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 58",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 14",
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 75",
      "answer": 153
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 55",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 60",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 17",
      "answer": 31
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 53",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 70",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 33",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 95",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 60",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 53",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 49",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 10",
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 97",
      "answer": 160
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 35",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 35",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 98",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 100",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 69",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 74",
      "answer": 151
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 53",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 10",
      "answer": 41
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 45",
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 20",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 21",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 78",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 95",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 57",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 4",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 44",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 85",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 67",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 93",
      "answer": 160
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 41",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 85",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 22",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 54",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 40",
      "answer": 46
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 93",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 63",
      "answer": 135
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 22",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 30",
      "answer": 114
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 18,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 1700,
      "to": 1800
    }
  }
}